{
    "subject": "resource/V_Corps_(Grande_Arm\u00e9e)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableCommander",
    "object": "resource/J\u00f3zef_Poniatowski",
    "human_readable": "J\u00f3zef Poniatowski was a notable commander of the V Corps (Grande Arm\u00e9e).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9645650386810303,
            "question": "Was J\u00f3zef Poniatowski a commander?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8951481580734253,
            "question": "Who was J\u00f3zef Poniatowski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8347619771957397,
            "question": "Was J\u00f3zef Poniatowski a military leader?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8206901550292969,
            "question": "In what capacity was J\u00f3zef Poniatowski notable?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8025914430618286,
            "question": "What was the role of the V Corps in the Grande Arm\u00e9e?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7583509683609009,
            "question": "Which military force did J\u00f3zef Poniatowski lead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6978302597999573,
            "question": "To which military force did J\u00f3zef Poniatowski belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6900659203529358,
            "question": "What was the Grande Arm\u00e9e?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6869678497314453,
            "question": "Describe J\u00f3zef Poniatowski's military contributions."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5001519918441772,
            "question": "What was the V Corps known as?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=J\u00f3zef Poniatowski was a notable commander of the V Corps (Grande Arm\u00e9e).",
            "html": "dbpedia_7556_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe J\u00f3zef Poniatowski's military contributions.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7556_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the Grande Arm\u00e9e?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7556_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which military force did J\u00f3zef Poniatowski belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7556_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7556_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide information about J\u00f3zef Poniatowski's military career and his role as a leader in the Polish insurrection against the Prussian kingdom, the Austro-Polish War, and Napoleon's armies. They also mention that he was appointed by Napoleon as the leader of the V corps of the Grande Arm\u00e9e, which is composed entirely of Poles. This information supports the claim that J\u00f3zef Poniatowski was a notable commander of the V Corps (Grande Arm\u00e9e)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about J\u00f3zef Poniatowski's military role, including his command over the V Corps during Napoleon's Russian campaign. For example, the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7556/re-ranker-msmarco/42.txt` states: \"Napoleon appointed Poniatowski the leader of the V corps of the great army, which was entirely composed of Poles.\" This supports the query that J\u00f3zef Poniatowski was a notable commander of the V Corps (Grande Arm\u00e9e)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}